to ask a question you will need to press star one and one on your telephone and wait for your name
to be announced to withdraw your question please press star one and one again we will now take your
first question and the question comes from the line of emily field from barclays please go ahead
hi thank you so much for taking my question um i just wanted to ask um for a bit more context just
on the natalie delay of the paducah in the united states can you confirm that this was you know
very specific to the manufacturing issue and that the fda did not ask for any additional information
with regards to any of the subgroups or you know any additional information from the clinical trials
thank you yeah thanks emily so this was only related to the cmc issue uh where we've already
initiated label discussions with the fda we submitted some additional uh data to support
provision to the cmc package with that we had the standard a three-month extension because we
have a
a
, we submitted that additional data so that extends the paducah out by three months
we believe now we're well on track having finalized the submission of that data for
an approval inside of q3 next question operator thank you your next question comes from the line
of florence says peders from bernstein please go ahead good afternoon thank you
very much for taking my question a quick question on cost and ticks um and the new indication
in hs could you give us uh some color on how you see the hs opportunity going forward as it seems
that you are gaining new patients as you have a new treatment more potentially the existing one
but there will be also new in trends in the coming years so some color on this hs market
opportunity would be great thank you yeah thanks florent as you know historically uh
only anti-tnfs adalimumab was the only medicine available for this model and i think that's a very strong
for the delivery and as you know historically anti-tnf had limumab was the only medicine available
biologic medicine available for these patients. And so I think the market had not grown to its
full potential. I mean, HS is a relatively prevalent dermatological disease. I think
it's second most prevalent after psoriasis, or second or third most prevalent after psoriasis.
So I think it's something that's really a big unmet need. So I would expect there to be a
significant expansion in the market as more entrants come in. And we continue to believe
that Cosentix and HS alone are a billion-dollar medicine. So we're very optimistic on Cosentix,
Outlook, and HS, even with other entrants coming in, simply because there is so much unmet need.
Most patients are not on biologics, or many of these patients have dropped out of the system
and are not receiving care at all. Now that physicians know that there are safe options
available, we believe more and more patients will be brought in. We see that broad-based globally.
So I mentioned as well, we see strong HS uptake for Cosentix in the U.S., as well as in EU and
international markets. So we think it could be an attractive market in the long run. And we also
have a pipeline we're developing as future agents to follow on for Cosentix in HS. Now in phase
two studies, but over as it matures, we're excited about, can we actually address HS with
even higher efficacy medicines over time? Thank you very much.
Next question. Operator, thank you, Colin.
Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Emanuele Papadakis from Deutsche Bank. Please
go ahead. Thank you for taking the question. The pipeline question on Ionalamab, she pulled
forward the readout in Sjogren's 2025. So just the drivers for that, confidence on probability of
success, and there's been a number of competitor updates, and that's based recently. So just
perhaps you could refresh us with your thoughts on the magnitude of SDI improvement you're hoping
to show, and indeed, whether you still consider that to be the right and definitive endpoint. Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, Emanuele. So absolutely, we saw very fast enrollment, higher,
faster than expected enrollment for Ionalamab in Sjogren's. We have pulled forward that readout.